Bradley Neve

Recent graduate from the University of Leeds. I am someone who enjoys working in teams, relishes the prospect of new and exciting challenges and thrives when tasked with solving problems. This affinity for problem solving led me to a study mathematics beyond school, and into university.

During my degree, the interactions I had with coding – in particular with Python - brought to light a desire to pursue a career in the field of technology. This pursuit is now underway, and I am thrilled to see what the future of this has to offer.

SUMMARY

I attained a 2:1 in a Mathematics MMath degree, and I am currently a Tech Trainee at futureproof.

I have experience working as a vaccine administration assistant, a picker packer, and various hospitality roles

I am now looking forward to beginning what I hope to be a long and accomplished career in technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

futureproof | Tech Trainee | August 2022 - October 2022

- 13-week bootcamp covering the main areas of web development, including JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Databases, and Python. Touched on the usage of python as a tool for data science and analytics.
- Completed 3 group projects (will be 4), most recently a 1-week group project using React to create a trivia quiz, using Jest and Enzyme to test. (Projects are available to view on my portfolio, linked in the find out more section).
- Practiced an agile methodology to get large projects completed in a short time scale.
- Learnt good practices of version control using GitHub.
- Enhanced my ability to learn efficiently, especially in the applications of coding languages. Spent the first 3 laps (10 weeks) of the course learning and practicing JavaScript, then covered Python in the same regard in just one week.

Liverpool Heart and Chest Hospital | Vaccine Administration Assistant | February 2021 - June 2021

- Welcomed, guided, and administered vaccine centre visitors in a professional, fast-paced and everchanging environment. This often involved managing a great number of patients within the centre.
- Proposed and implemented computational techniques to help streamline daily numerical tasks for the managerial team.

Picker Packer | DPD Warehouse | June 2020 - September 2020

- Operated a large-scale industrial cross belt conveyor system in an efficient manner under high time pressure to meet organisation deadlines and targets.

EDUCATION

University of Leeds | September 2018 - June 2022 |

Mathematics/MMATH - 2:1

St Edward's College | September 2016 – June 2018 |

Mathematics - A*, Further Mathematics - A, Physics - A

HOBBIES/INTERESTS

- Chess Music
- Hiking Gaming
- Rugby Football

FIND OUT MORE

<u>bradneve</u>

n Bradley Neve

bradleyneve

Brad.neve@gmail.com

07711162392

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Command Line Interface

Git/GitHub

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

React

Python

Bootstrap

R

Docker

Latex

Excel

PROFFSSIONAL SKILLS

Teamwork

Problem Solving

Leadership

Communication